It's okay if you don't like me back.
Huh?
I'm just happy I could tell
you how I feel, Mayama.
I won't ask for anything more.
- But...
- Think about it.
You're like a comforting
presence to me, Mayama.
I guess I like you the way
someone likes a local mascot.
What is that supposed to mean?
I'm being serious...
So, was this all just in my head?
You should have told me sooner.
I've already fallen for you for real.
Summer vacation is full of temptations.
But you all need to remember
you're students of Kitahara High.
Spend your days with
integrity and discipline.
Yes, ma'am.
Well then, have a great summer vacation.
Yeah! Let's go! Let's
go! Come on, baby! Yeah!
Yeah! Yeah!
Summer vacation!
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
Whoo!
Mayama.
Hmm?
Why are you so down?
Come on, summer
vacation has officially started!
Go, go, summer vacation!
You're way too hyped.
I talked to Tsunekawada.
Do you want the four of us to go on a trip?
It's summer, after all. The
beach sounds nice, right?
Ah...
Do you hate the beach?
Then let's do the opposite
and go to the mountains,
or the opposite of the
opposite and hit the hot springs.
What even is the opposite of the opposite?
Sorry.
For summer vacation... well...
I'm getting a part-time job.
I'll be busy working.
I'm gonna take off.
Hey!
What's his deal?
Should the three of us go, then?
Oh, how about camping?
The opposite of the
opposite of the opposite.
I don't even know anymore.
"After Moving Seats, The Boy Behind Me Has A Crush On Me"
(Episode 6)
Since I already said I'd be busy working...
I figured I might as
well actually get a job.
I thought if I just buried
myself in something else...
I could forget about Asamiya.
But...
This kind of work is definitely
not meant for summer.
Okay.
I'm finally almost done handing these out.
We don't allow flyers here.
I'm sorry.
Sakaki?
Scared you, didn't I?
My vocal range...
Huh? What are you doing here?
What do you mean? This
is my apartment building.
Oh.
I see.
I'll get going, then.
Huh? Where are you going?
Didn't you say flyers aren't allowed here?
I was just messing with you.
You can put them in, it's fine.
Here, let me help.
Huh?
How do you do this?
I've never done it before.
Huh?
Thanks, you're a lifesaver.
Don't mention it.
By the way, you really
did get a part-time job.
Huh?
I thought you just made up an excuse
because you didn't want to go on the trip.
No, it's not that...
Seems like something's on your mind.
What...?
You've just been really gloomy
since the cultural festival ended.
Even an oblivious guy like me can tell.
You don't have to talk
about it if you don't want to.
Hey, Sakaki.
You've had a few girlfriends before, right?
Yeah, unlike you.
I was just wondering what it
actually means to like someone.
Huh?
Are you writing a poem or something?
No.
I'm being serious.
Well...
For me, if I like someone...
I want to be with her and I want to
touch her. Something like that, I guess.
But isn't there anything else?
Like not being able to
see them romantically?
Oh, you mean liking them as a friend?
Yeah...
I think I get what's bothering you.
But that might just be because
you lack romantic experience.
I can't deny that.
You really need to get out there
and meet more people, Mayama.
I happen to be single right now, too.
Huh?
What does you being
single have to do with this?
It's super important.
Ah.
There's still one spot left.
You're done with work for today, right?
Yeah...
Then let's go.
Huh? Wait a sec...
Huh?
Where exactly are we going?
Karaoke.
Huh?
But this isn't just any ordinary karaoke.
Sakaki.
Oh.
Don't tell me this is...
A mixer at karaoke!
You didn't tell me it was this!
Didn't you want to understand women?
I never said that!
Alright, alright, alright.
I'm...
Huh? Isn't that Sakaki and Mayama?
Asamiya...
What are you guys doing?
Just hanging out.
What about you?
Isn't it obvious?
Ah... wait a minute.
A mixer.
You really love these things, Sakaki.
Which means Mayama is...
No, I'm...
Mayama insisted on coming.
He wouldn't take no for an answer.
Let's go.
Come on, come on.
Get in, get in!
What are you doing?
Ah, wait a sec!
Thanks!
Nice to meet you all today.
Great singing!
Here.
Introduce yourself and pick a song.
Huh?
Ah...
Here you go.
I'm Mayama.
That's it.
As for a song... maybe later.
Next, then!
Asamiya definitely got the wrong idea.
Thanks for waiting.
Here's your iced coffee.
You really surprised me earlier.
I never thought you'd
go to a mixer, Mayama.
Sorry for calling you out of the blue.
I was a little surprised.
After all, this is the first time
you've come to me for advice.
So, what's up?
There's someone I like.
Hmm...
You're not surprised?
Huh?
No, I am surprised.
Because I've never heard you
talk about this kind of thing before.
Yeah.
So...
What kind of person are they?
They're really kind.
They always put other people's
feelings before his own.
Yeah.
Before I knew it, I had
already fallen for them.
I even told them how I felt.
But...
They didn't like you back?
I was the one who said it was
okay if they didn't like me back.
What do you mean?
Because they're a kind person.
Too kind.
I think right now, he's trying desperately
to respond to everyone's feelings.
Thinking they have to like
me back for my sake.
Something like that.
There might come a day when they
just force themselves to accommodate me.
That wouldn't work, right?
Because that's not what I want.
If he genuinely fell for
me, of course I'd be happy.
But if that's not the case...
Then...
It wouldn't be his true feelings,
which is what I really want.
So...
You're dealing with a
pretty tough romance, huh.
Huh?
No, it's just...
I just suddenly realized that you worry about
these things just like any normal person.
I'm seriously asking for your advice here.
My bad, my bad.
But seriously,
it's my first time talking to
someone about this kind of thing.
It's super embarrassing.
I'm actually glad to see this side of you.
Huh?
Why don't you just show that
person this side of you too?
Everything you just said,
all those confusing feelings you have,
if you just tell them properly,
they'll definitely understand.
Or do you not trust them?
You don't trust the
person you've fallen for?
It's not that.
I'd really love to meet them.
What kind of person could make
Asamiya fall so hard?
Ah...
Yeah.
Mayama.
Anyway, I'm rooting for you.
Nice singing.
Really?
That was awesome.
What made you choose this song?
I'm gonna go to the restroom...
Don't be jealous.
- His pronunciation was spot on.
- No way.
Um...
I thought he was American.
I know, right?
It suddenly makes me
want to fly overseas for a trip.
By the way, that guy we ran into
earlier who seemed like Sakaki's friend...
Yeah?
His name is Asamiya, right?
He's super hot, isn't he?
Totally.
He's on a whole other level. I think I'm a little in love.
Don't you have a boyfriend?
How should I put it?
He's in a different category.
Huh? Why are you even at a mixer then?
There's no way Asamiya could
actually like someone like me.
It was impossible from the very beginning.
I came here today behind his back.
Then just find someone else today.
Oh.
What are you doing here?
I came looking for you.
For me?
Yeah. And after I found you,
you were just standing here frozen for
some reason, so I was just watching you.
Wait a minute.
Go home.
Weren't you the one
who drew the line first, Asamiya?
- Oh, welcome back.
- Welcome back.
Here.
It's about time Mayama sang a song too.
Yeah.
Huh? Seriously?
Can you sing?
What are you gonna sing?
- Sing a Western song.
- Stop messing around.
Asamiya?
It's that hot guy from earlier.
Let's go.
What's going on?
Did you have fun at the mixer?
I was just dragged there.
Sakaki sure is lucky.
He gets to put his arm around you.
Have you ever done this with Sakaki?
Of course not.
What about this?
How does it feel to have
me hold your hand like this?
I don't know.
I've never done anything like this before.
But you're blushing.
I haven't been able to see
you since summer break started.
I've been so frustrated.
I've been wanting to do this, to really
feel that you're right here beside me.
You're so unfair.
When you say things like that,
what am I supposed to do?
I don't understand you at all, Asamiya.
You were the one who drew the line first.
So don't just cross it again.
I'm sorry.
In my own way, I was...
thinking really seriously
about you, Asamiya.
Though someone as perfect as you
probably wouldn't understand how I feel.
I'm not perfect at all.
Huh?
You heard them earlier, right?
My whole life has been like that.
People only judge me by my looks.
People have high expectations, but the moment
I fail, they're quick to sneer and say,
"He's just a pretty face after all."
That's why I've always tried so hard.
To be honest, I'm panicking right now too.
The overwhelming happiness of being with you
that makes me feel like I'm losing control,
the desire to not hurt you,
the urge to clear up the misunderstanding,
all these feelings are mixed up together.
Even so,
I still want to look cool in front of you.
I always end up unconsciously acting
like I've got everything under control.
What misunderstanding...
are you talking about?
You're not some local mascot.
If you didn't actually like me, Mayama,
but forced yourself to like me to
spare my feelings, that would really hurt.
That's why I said those things.
Eh...
But...
I was completely wrong.
I'm sorry.
So... when you said you liked me before,
it wasn't just as a friend, but...
Of course I meant it romantically.
I want to hold your hand.
I want to hug you, and...
I want to spend more time with you, Mayama.
Mayama?
Thank goodness...
I thought... it was already hopeless.
I'm sorry.
I would never force myself to like you
just to spare your feelings, Asamiya.
So please don't draw that line again.
Okay.
Because I like you, Asamiya.
What kind of "like"?
Huh?
I feel like I've made
my feelings pretty clear.
So I want to hear it from you too, Mayama.
Your "like"...
What kind of "like" is it?
I want to touch you.
I want to hold your hand too.
I want to hug you.
It's that kind of "like."
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
I don't hate it.
Your phone is ringing.
I really want to see you soon.
Kou-chan.
(Next Episode)
Hi, I'm his boyfriend.
I know.
(Tanabata Festival)
Do you want to go together?
It'd be nice if we could do something
that feels like summer.
I didn't expect it to be
an event part-time job.
Kou-chan.
What's her relationship with Asamiya?